MUWAHEED MUSTAPHA

Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria · +234 813 181 8664 muwaheedmustapha@gmail.com . GitHub . Portfolio-Website

A **Software developer** looking to enhance my professional skills, capabilities, and knowledge in an organization that recognizes the value of hard work and trusts me with responsibilities and challenges. I have 2 years of experience working with python, its libraries, and frameworks, coupled with extended experience in JavaScript to develop web and desktop applications. Portfolio-Website

EXPERIENCE

JUNE 2022 - SEPT 2022

BACKEND DEVELOPER, SEEDBUILDERS INNOVATION HUB

- Managed web applications and worked with the development team to develop a Business intelligence software.
- In charge of handling the backend, data extraction, and cleaning using Flask, SQL, and Pandas.

JULY 2021 - OCT 2021

NETWORK SECURITY INTERN, GALAXY BACKBONE LTD

- Successfully completed 3-month internship in network security, gaining experience in networking, cyber security, and email security appliances.
- Created presentations and exported firewall policies using Python, resulting in increased efficiency and productivity.

EDUCATION

2017 - 2023

B.ENG COMPUTER ENGINEERING, BAYERO UNIVERSITY KANO, NIGERIA CGPA of 4.71/5.00

SKILLS

Front-End Development: Html, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React

Back-End Development: Python, Flask, Jinja, ORM, SQL Alchemy, SQL, MySQL, C#, REST, Git

Data Science: Data Extraction and Visualization, Data Analytics, Python (Pandas, Numpy, Scikit-Learn, Seaborn, Matplotlib), SQL, MySQL, Regression Analysis